Amari Jones

I am a extremely intelligent hardworking woman seeking employment.

Rolling Fork, MS 39159 amarijones57@gmail.com 6629070886

Results driven Assistant Manager with 3+ years of experience in the food service industry. Determined to provide superior guest experiences by energetically and expertly coordinating, managing, and motivating team members.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Assistant Manager

Parsotam Mexican Restaurant - Rolling Fork, MS June 2015 to Present

My responsibilities within this job were recruiting, training, and supervising staff,agreeing and managing budgets, planning menus, ensuring compliance with licensing, hygiene and health and safety guidelines, promoting and marketing the business,overseeing stock levels, ordering supplies,producing staff rotas.

General Laborer / Housekeeper

Cottonwood Plantation - Mayersville, MS March 2012 to November 2015

- *Protecting equipment and making sure there are no inadequacies
- *Cleaning activities such as sweeping, mopping, dusting and polishing
- *cleaning and preparing the shop, loading and delivering materials
- *Lift heavy loads up to 80lbs
- *General maintenance of equipment

Front Desk Clerk

Merit heritage - Rolling Fork, MS July 2013 to May 2015

Record all health care records, keep up with patients data. Check patients in and out of facility. Provide great customer service.

Student Worker

WWISSCAA - Rolling Fork, MS September 2014 to February 2015

Responsibilities

Stocking and Computer Operator

Education

High school or equivalent in General Studies

South Delta High School - Rolling Fork, MS 2011 to 2015

Accounting

Mississippi Delta Community College - Moorhead, MS

Skills

Microsoft Office, Communication, Multitasking, Prioritizing, Organization. ... Technical skills. ... Interpersonal skills. ... Initiative and problem-solving abilities Dependability, Customer Service, Management, Stocking, Mentoring, Key Holder, Fast Food, Retail Management